Hi, good morning. I'm so glad you came. I was worried no one would show up in this weather.
So, whoa. I'm glad you're okay.
Okay. So, just a couple of announcements, questions that are received via email.
A few things before we jump into the material.
First of all, I was asked, so who is this class for?
is it for people you know it's positive psychology only for people who are very happy is it only for people who are depressed is it who's who's this class for well the class is for anyone who's
interested in positive psychology and anyone who wants to be happier if you're extremely happy you can still be happier if you're very unhappy you can still be happier so the class essentially
is for everyone who's interested in the material and i would add someone who's interested to to work, to put the kind of effort that we talked about last time, which is not the kind of
effort that would require you to, you know, just wreck your head about understanding a certain concept, but it is effort in terms of applying these ideas to your lives.
Now, you may want to take this class because you're...